A Guide to the Papers of the Virginia Daughters of the American Revolution, 1980-1983
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Virginia Daughters of the American Revolution 1980-1983
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
6884-f
This collection consists of 26 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift on 11 March 1983.
Contents List
- Virginia Counties
  - Tombstone Inscriptions and Bible Records from Campbell, Bedford, Pittsylvania, Richmond, and Appomattox Counties, Virginia. 1982 (Box 1)
  - A List of Classes in Culpeper County for January 1781 for Recruiting this State's Quota of Troops to Serve in the Continental Army 1983 (Box 1)
  - Marriage Records, Halifax County, Virginia ca. 1750-1800, Part I 1982 (Box 1)
  - Wills and Some Deeds, Halifax County, Virginia c. 1750-18--, Part II 1981 (Box 1)
  - Tombstones in St. Luke's Church Cemetery and St. Luke's Memorial Park Cemetery, Smithfield, Virginia - Isle of Wight County, 1632-1980, Vols. I and II 1981, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Bible Records Primarily Northampton County, Virginia-Vol. IV 1982 (Box 1)
  - Gravestone Inscriptions in Northampton County, Virginia 1980 (Box 1)
  - Cemetery Records, Orange County, Virginia, Vol. V 1981, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Orange Review Obituaries and Other Genealogical Information, Vol. VI 1982, 2 folders (Box 2)
  - John M. Oakey Funeral Home Records, 1863-1969, Salem Virginia 1981 (Box 2)
  - Cemetery Records, Spotsylvania County, Virginia, Vol. IV 1981 (Box 2)
  - Records of Thompson Settlement Church, Jonesville, Va. 1983 (Box 2)
- Virginia Families
  - Barkley, Henley, Fleet, Randolph and Allied Families, Vol. I, A-G 1981, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Barkley, Henley, Fleet, Randolph and Allied Families, Vol. II, A-G 1981, 1 folder (Box 3)
  - Sketch of the New River Pioneer (Cox Family) 1983 (Box 3)
  - Speaks Family Records, Virginia and Cedar Grove Church Records, Tennessee 1982 (Box 3)
  - Stewart, Verlett, Herman, Wood, Pickett and Wyatt Families 1983 (Box 3)
  - Ledger and Family Records of Summers Family, Northern Virginia, 1762-1980 1981 (Box 3)
  - Woodhouse Family 1983 (Box 3)
- Bible, Family, and Legal Records
  - Bible Records of Virginia 1982, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Cemetery and Church Records 1983 (Box 4)
  - Family Records of Virginia 1981 (Box 4)
  - Marriage Records of Virginia 1982 (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous Records of Virginia 1983 (Box 4)
  - Wills of Virginia 1983, 2 folders (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous
  - The Nelson County Pioneer, Nelson County, Kentucky 1983 (Box 4)